YOU LOOK CUTE IN BUBBLES.
AH, YOU'RE JUST ALL LIQUORED UP.
( knock on door )
Joey:
HEY, IT'S ME.
I'M COMING IN.
I'VE HAD A VERY LONG, HARD DAY.
I'M GETTING CHICKEN.
YOU WANT SOME?
NO, THANKS. NO CHICKEN.
BYE-BYE THEN.
OKAY.
YOU SURE? SOME EXTRA CRISPY?
DIRTY RICE? BEANS?
FOR THE LAST TIME, NO.
GET OUT. GET OUT, JOEY.
ALL RIGHT.
( gasping )
ARE YOU OKAY?
I'M SO SORRY. HE WOULDN'T LEAVE.
HE KEPT ASKING
IF I WANTED CHICKEN.
CHICKEN?
I COULD EAT SOME CHICKEN.
HEY, JOE!
YEAH, COULD I GET A THREE-PIECE,
SOME COLE SLAW
AND SOME BEANS AND A COKE...
( screaming )
...DIET COKE.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
HEY!
HEY, PHEEBS!
OH, I HAVE TO TELL
YOU THIS STORY.
I WAS COMING OVER HERE
AND THIS CAB DRIVER...
WAS HIS NAME ANGUS?
( all laughing )
WHAT?
HE WAS THIS CAB DRIVER
WE HAD IN LONDON.
OH. HA-HA-HA.
ALL RIGHT, ANYWAY...
Monica:
WHAT WAS THAT PLACE
THAT PUB HE TOOK US TO?
THE WHEAT SHEAF.
AND THEY HAD THAT BEER,
THAT, UH...
BODDINGTON'S.
THAT'S IT, BABY.
OH, PHEEBS WAS GOING
TO TELL A STORY.
OKAY, SO, HE HAD
A REALLY FUNNY HAT.
I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT.
HEY.
HEY, ROSS.
BODDINGTON'S.
YEAH!
OH, MAN.
THAT WAS GOOD BEER.
YOU KNOW, I'D WALK
BACK TO LONDON
FOR ANOTHER FROSTY ONE
OF THOSE BAD BOYS.
YOU KNOW, I THINK
THEY HAVE THOSE
AT THAT BRITISH PUB
BY THE TRADE CENTER.
LATER.
ISN'T RACHEL SUPPOSED
TO BE BACK BY NOW?
HER PLANE GOT
DELAYED IN ATHENS
BUT, ACTUALLY, SHE SHOULD
BE HERE BY NOW.
S-SO YOU TALKED TO HER?
DID SHE... DID SHE SOUND MAD?
NO, BUT SHE LIKES ME.
YOU ABANDONED HER ON A PLANE.
OKAY, I DID NOT ABANDON RACHEL,
OKAY?
EMILY SHOWED UP AT THE AIRPORT.
I HAD TO GO AFTER HER.
I MEAN, I DID WHAT I HAD TO DO.
SHE'S MY WIFE.
RACHEL IS MY WIFE, YOU KNOW.
EMILY!
EMILY IS MY WIFE.
MAN, WHAT IS THAT?
SO YOU STILL HAVEN'T HEARD
FROM EMILY?
NO, NOT SINCE I LOST HER
AT THE AIRPORT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
SHE CAN OUTRUN YOU, MAN.
HEY, SHE'S FAST, OKAY?
OH, YOU THINK
YOU CAN BEAT ME?
LET'S GO, OUTSIDE!
HI.
RACHEL!
HI!
RACH, RACH, I AM SO SORRY.
I AM SO, SO SORRY.
OH, ROSS, COME ON.
YOU JUST DID
WHAT YOU HAD TO DO.
THAT'S IT?
YOU'RE NOT MAD?
I MEAN,
IT MUST HAVE BEEN TERRIBLE.
TERRIBLE? HELL,
I WAS IN GREECE.
THAT WAS A NICE HOTEL.
NICE BEACH.
MET THE NICE PEOPLE.
NOT TOO SHABBY FOR RACHEL.
SO, WHAT? THAT'S IT?
WELL, YEAH.
WE'RE COOL.
TOTALLY COOL.
THANKS, RACH.
OH, YOU'RE THE BEST.
OH, NO, YOU'RE THE BEST.
OH, I GOT TO GO
TO THE FLOWER STORE.
CHECK IT OUT.
NO ONE WILL TELL ME
WHERE EMILY IS.
SO I'M GOING TO SEND
72 LONG-STEMMED RED ROSES
TO HER PARENTS' HOUSE.
ONE FOR EACH DAY
THAT I'VE KNOWN AND LOVED HER.
THAT OUGHT TO GET HER
TALKING TO ME AGAIN.
OH, ROSS, WHEN YOU MAKE OUT
THE CARD
BE SURE TO MAKE IT OUT
TO EMILY.
RACH, THAT'S GREAT.
IT'S SO GOOD YOU HAD SUCH
A GOOD TIME IN GREECE.
WHAT?
I DIDN'T HAVE A GOOD TIME
IN GREECE.
ROSS ABANDONED ME, OKAY?
I COULDN'T GET A PLANE OUT
SO I HAD TO STAY
IN THEIR HONEYMOON SUITE
WITH PEOPLE COMING UP TO ME
ALL THE TIME, GOING
"OH, MRS. GELLER, WHY YOU CRY?"
I MEAN, IT WAS SO HUMILIATING.
I FELT
LIKE SUCH AN IDIOT.
I MEAN, IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
AND YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE I MAKE
VERY BAD DECISIONS.
OH, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
YES, IT IS. IT IS TRUE.
I WENT AFTER ROSS
IN STUPID LONDON.
LONDON IS STUPID. STUPID.
PHOEBE, YOU WERE RIGHT.
I SHOULD NEVER HAVE GONE
TO LONDON
AND FROM NOW ON
YOU MAKE
ALL MY DECISIONS FOR ME.
OH, NO, I DID THAT
FOR SOMEONE ONCE.
I'M NOT COMFORTABLE
HAVING THAT KIND OF POWER
AND CONTROL OVER
SOMEONE'S LIFE.
I'LL DO IT.
Rachel:
THAT'S FINE.
SO, MONICA, YOU ARE NOW
IN CHARGE OF MY LOVE LIFE.
OKAY, I GOT TO GO TO WORK.
AND RACHEL,
GREAT TO HAVE YOU BACK.
PHEEBS!
ALWAYS A PLEASURE.
OH, RACHEL, SWEETIE, LOOK.
HERE'S A REALLY
CUTE PICTURE
OF YOU AND JOEY
AT THE RECEPTION.
OH, HE'S MARRIED.
ROSS IS MARRIED.
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
HONEY, SWEETIE, BY THE EDGES.
I MEAN, I'M JUST GOING
TO HAVE TO ACCEPT IT.
OH!
IT'S MY FAULT.
SWEETIE... EDGES...
FINGERS...
SMUDGY...
OH, MY GOD! AH!
THAT'S OKAY.
I KNOW THAT YOU'RE VERY UPSET
RIGHT NOW.
I KNOW THAT WASN'T ABOUT ME.
I BET IT WAS ABOUT HER
A LITTLE.
IF YOU STOPPED THINKING
ABOUT ROSS
YOU WOULD NOTICE
THERE WERE GREAT GUYS
EVERYWHERE.
NOW, LOOK...
GUNTHER.
I MEAN...
HE'S NICE. HE'S CUTE.
YEAH, I GUESS GUNTHER IS...
OR HOW ABOUT
THAT GUY
OVER THERE?
THAT IS THE GUY
YOU FLIRTED WITH
AT THE COUNTER
THAT TIME.
OH, I DON'T KNOW,
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU'RE GOING TO TALK TO HIM.
WE MADE A DEAL.
I MAKE YOUR DECISIONS
AND I SAY YOU'RE GOING
TO TALK TO HIM.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE THE BOSS.
I GUESS I GOT TO DO
WHAT YOU TELL ME.
SAY THAT TO HIM
AND YOU'RE GOLDEN.
HEY.
HEY, PHEEBS.
WE GOT OUR PICTURES
FROM LONDON.
HERE'S ALL OF US
AT THE TOWER OF LONDON...
OH, YEAH, THERE WE ALL ARE.
YEAH, THERE'S ROSS AND JOEY
AND YOU AND...
AND ME.
WE'VE BEEN TALKING
ABOUT LONDON TOO MUCH,
HAVEN'T WE?
NO, I'M SORRY.
IT'S JUST
'CAUSE I COULDN'T BE THERE
'CAUSE ALL I EVER GET TO DO NOW
IS PREGNANT STUFF.
IT JUST BUMS ME OUT.
SORRY.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WELL, YOU KNOW,
A LITTLE OF THIS
A LITTLE OF THAT.
I GOT MYSELF A DATE
TOMORROW NIGHT.
SEE? DIDN'T I TELL YOU?
YOU'RE GETTING OVER ROSS
ALREADY.
GET OUT.
WHAT TOOK YOU SO LONG?
I GOT CAUGHT UP AT WORK
BUT I'M QUITTING TOMORROW.
SO, THANKS FOR
HAVING ME OVER.
RACH.
PHEEBS.
SEE YA!
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
PROBABLY SOME
EUROPEAN GOOD-BYE THING
HE PICKED UP IN LONDON.
I DON'T...
IT'S NOT EUROPEAN.
WELL, IT FELT FRENCH.
OH, GOD, I REALLY
HAD A GOOD TIME.
YEAH, ME, TOO.
( sighing )
SO, I GUESS THIS IS IT.
YEAH, UM...
UNLESS YOU WANT
TO COME INSIDE.
YEAH.
OKAY... OH, UH...
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I, UH...
I CAN'T DECIDE THIS.
UM...
OKAY, JUST HOLD
ON A SECOND.
YEAH.
UH, HI.
HI.
IS MONICA AROUND?
I HAVE TO ASK HER SOMETHING.
DOING HER LAUNDRY.
WHAT'S THAT?
IT CAME IN THE
MAIL TODAY.
IT'S 72 LONG-STEMMED RED ROSES
ONE FOR EACH DAY
I'VE KNOWN AND LOVED EMILY
CUT UP INTO MULCH.
OH, HONEY,
THAT'S AWFUL.
OH, IT'S NOT SO BAD.
MONICA'S GOING
TO MAKE POTPOURRI.
I THINK I'M GOING
TO GO WANDER OUT
IN THE RAIN
FOR A WHILE.
BUT IT'S NOT RAINING.
I CAN'T CATCH A BREAK.
YOU KNOW WHAT, ROSS?
YOU'RE NOT GOING
ANYWHERE.
YOU'RE GOING TO SIT
RIGHT HERE.
I'M GOING TO MAKE YOU
A CUP OF TEA
AND WE'RE GOING TO TALK
THIS WHOLE THING OUT.
ALL RIGHT?
HEY, DAVE.
YEAH.
LISTEN, I'M GOING TO
NEED TO TAKE A RAIN CHECK.
MY ROOMMATE IS
JUST REALLY SICK.
OKAY? BYE.
HONEY, LISTEN...
I KNOW...
GOD, I KNOW
THINGS SEEM SO BAD...
RACH?
COULD I TALK TO YOU
JUST FOR A MINUTE?
I DROPPED SOME SOCKS.
YEAH.
WHAT IS THE MATTER
WITH YOU?
DO YOU WANT TO FALL
INTO THE TRAP?
DO YOU WANT
TO FALL INTO THE TRAP?
YOU DID NOT
DROP ANY SOCKS!
DAVE TOLD ME
YOU BLEW HIM OFF.
YOU LISTEN TO ME.
I'M CALLING THE SHOTS.
I SAY YOU LEAVE ROSS ALONE
AND GO GET DAVE.
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
TRYING TO DO?
WELL, ULTIMATELY,
I WAS TRYING...
YOU KNOW, I WANTED...
TO TELL HIM I WAS
STILL IN LOVE WITH HIM.
WHAT?
YOU CANNOT TELL HIM THAT.
WHY? WHY NOT?
PEOPLE LOVE
TO HEAR THAT.
I MAKE THE DECISIONS
AND I SAY "NO."
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
NO, YOU DON'T MAKE
MY DECISIONS
BECAUSE... YOU'RE FIRED.
( gasps )
YOU CAN'T FIRE ME.
I MAKE YOUR DECISIONS AND I SAY
I'M NOT FIRED. HA!
WELL...
( gasps )
RACHEL!
COME ON,
LET ME IN.
HAVING SOME TROUBLE?
RACHEL LOCKED THE DOOR.
I'LL KICK THAT DOOR IN
IF YOU GIVE ME A LITTLE SUGAR.
OH! RACHEL!
RA... LET ME IN!
RACHEL?
( pounding )
THANK YOU.
RACHEL... CAN I TALK
TO YOU OUTSIDE FOR A SEC?
NO.
I REALLY NEED
TO TALK TO YOU.
WELL, THEN, TALK.
OKAY, I WILL.
REMEMBER THAT THING
THAT WE JUST DISCUSSED
THAT YOU WANTED TO DO?
YES.
WHAT THING?
Monica:
WELL...
RACHEL WANTS TO TAKE
SWING DANCE LESSONS...
WHICH I THINK IS
A REALLY STUPID IDEA.
IT'S DANGEROUS.
SHE'S NEVER GOING TO GET
WHAT SHE WANTS
AND WHO KNOWS
WHO SHE MIGHT
END UP HURTING?
MONICA'S RIGHT,
SWING DANCING CAN BE TRICKY.
I'M GOING
TO USE THE PHONE.
I GOT TO CANCEL
THOSE FIVE GIANT TEDDY BEARS
I SENT TO EMILY.
MY GOD,
THINK OF THE MASSACRE.
I'M GOING TO DO IT.
ALL RIGHT... RACHEL...
OKAY, I KNOW
YOU THINK I'M CRAZY
BUT BEFORE YOU TELL HIM
YOU LOVE HIM
JUST TRY TO FIND ONE PERSON
WHO THINKS THIS IS A GOOD IDEA
'CAUSE I BET YOU CAN'T.
BUT I R...
PLEASE!
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
( thud )
JOEY, I'M IN!
( Joey, painfully ):
ALL RIGHT, GOOD DEAL.
HEY...
PHEEBS!
PHOEBE!
Rachel:
HEY, PHEEBS.
UH...
OKAY... PHEEBS?
YEAH?
UM...
YOU KNOW HOW THE OTHER DAY
YOU WERE TALKING
ABOUT HOW YOU DIDN'T GET
TO GO TO LONDON
AND YOU WERE FEELING LEFT OUT?
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, WELL
WE ALL FELT REALLY BAD
ABOUT THAT
SO... WE DECIDED
THAT WE SHOULD ALL TAKE
A LITTLE TRIP TOGETHER.
OH, THAT'S SO NICE!
HOW GREAT! WHERE?
WHERE'S THE TRIP?
WELL...
WE THOUGHT WE WOULD ALL GO
TO A PICNIC...
( gasps )
IN CENTRAL PARK!
CENTRAL PARK?
YEAH, ALL OF US, ALL DAY.
THAT SUCKS.
THAT'S NOT A TRIP.
I JUST CAME
FROM THE PARK.
WHAT ARE WE GOING
TO HIGH-FIVE ABOUT
AT THE STUPID CENTRAL PARK?
WELL, IT'S RIGHT BY MY HOUSE.
ALL RIGHT!
WELL, I'M GOING TO GO HOME
AND BASK IN THE TRIUMPH
OF MY CENTRAL PARK IDEA.
HEY, WHOA!
HOLD ON A SEC THERE, MR. KISSY.
YOU KNOW
I'VE BEEN MEANING TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT THIS WHOLE, LITTLE,
NEW EUROPEAN THING
YOU'VE GOT GOING ON
AND I JUST NEED TO TELL YOU
IT MAKES ME VERY UNCOMFORTABLE
AND I JUST...
YOU KNOW, JUST STOP IT.
WELL, I WAS JUST TRYING
TO BRING A LITTLE CULTURE
TO THE GROUP.
THAT'S FINE, JUST DON'T
BRING IT IN MY MOUTH.
IT MAKES ME WANT
TO PUKE.
HEY, EVERYBODY,
PHEEBS IS HERE.
PHOEBE!
HEY, PHOEBE!
HEY, PHEEBS!
HEY, PHOEBE,
WHOO!
OKAY, WHOO, HI.
OKAY, PHEEBS...
WE DECIDED
THAT THE PICNIC
IDEA WAS A LITTLE...
YOU KNOW, IT
DIDN'T HAVE ANY...
WELL, IT BLEW.
SO...
WE THOUGHT THAT
THIS AFTERNOON
WE WOULD ALL GO AWAY
FOR THE WHOLE WEEKEND
TO ATLANTIC CITY.
OOH, ATLANTIC CITY!
OH, THAT'S A GREAT PLAN.
WHOSE PLAN WAS THAT?
MINE.
( excited gasp )
WAIT.
IT WAS MY PLAN.
Joey:
NO...
I SAID WE NEEDED
A NEW PLAN.
AND I CAME UP
WITH ATLANTIC CITY.
WHICH IS THE NEW PLAN.
( disbelieving grunt )
OKAY, WELL, WHY
DON'T WE, UM
ALL MEET UPSTAIRS
IN AN HOUR?
( excited gasp )
OKAY. OOH, ALL RIGHT,
I'M GOING TO GO PACK.
I'M GOING
TO GO PACK MY ASS OFF.
WHOO!
ALL RIGHT, COME ON,
RACH, LET'S GO.
YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GOING TO MEET YOU
UPSTAIRS IN A MINUTE.
NO.
RACHEL, YOU DIDN'T
FIND ANYONE
SO YOU CAN'T TELL HIM.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT DOESN'T MATTER.
OKAY, RACHEL, DO
YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW PAINFUL IT IS
TO TELL SOMEONE
THAT YOU LOVE THEM
AND NOT HAVE THEM
SAY IT BACK?
I-I DON'T CARE.
OKAY.
I-I CAN'T WATCH.
WHATCHA READING?
PAPER.
YEAH? WHAT'S
IT ABOUT?
EVENTS... FROM AROUND THE GLOBE.
OKAY.
( chuckles )
UH... ROSS,
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THERE'S SOMETHING
THAT I...
THAT I HAVE TO
TALK TO YOU ABOUT
AND EVERYBODY'S BEEN SAYING
THAT I SHOULDN'T TELL YOU
BUT I-I THINK THEY'RE WRONG.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW HOW
PEOPLE CAN BE WRONG.
SURE.
ONCE, AT WORK, I...
( laughs )
I THOUGHT CARBON DATING
OF FOSSILIZED...
OKAY, ROSS, I'M
REALLY TRYING
TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING HERE.
OH, UH...
YEAH.
OKAY.
GO AHEAD.
UM... OKAY.
I THINK I'M-I'M JUST GO...
I'M JUST GOING TO SAY IT.
I'M JUST GOING
TO SAY IT.
UH...
( sighs )
I'M STILL IN LOVE
WITH YOU... ROSS.
WOW.
UH...
HUH, I'M-I'M...
WOW, I'M NOT SURE
WHAT TO DO WITH THAT RIGHT NOW.
( laughing )
WH-WHAT? WAS THAT A JOKE?
'CAUSE IT'S MEAN.
( laughing )
I'M SO DEAD SERIOUS.
I'M TOTALLY SERIOUS.
WHY ARE YOU LAUGHING?
BECAU...
( laughing )
BECAUSE I
JUST HEARD IT.
I HEARD IT AND
IT'S RIDICULOUS!
I MEAN...
YOU'RE MARRIED.
YOU'RE MARRIED AND
IT'S JUST RIDICULOUS
AND IT'S, LIKE... IT'S,
LIKE, WHEN I SAID IT
I JUST SORT OF, LIKE,
I FLOATED UP OUT
OF MY BODY, YOU KNOW
AN-AND, THEN... AND, THEN, I
HEARD MYSELF SAY IT
AND, THEN, THE
FLOATING RACHEL...
WAS, LIKE, "YOU ARE
SUCH AN IDIOT!"
WELL... WELL, I AM MARRIED...
I KNOW.
EVEN THOUGH I HAVEN'T SPOKEN
TO MY WIFE SINCE THE WEDDING.
( laughing )
I'M SORRY,
THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
ACTUALLY, IT-IT KIND OF IS.
( chuckling )
MY WIFE WON'T RETURN MY CALLS.
( laughing )
I DON'T KNOW
WHERE MY WIFE IS.
OH, DARN.
( laughing )
"HEY, ROSS,
WHERE'S THE MISSUS?"
"DON'T KNOW."
( laughing )
OH... GOD.
OH...
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
DO YOU THINK... UH,
DO YOU THINK YOU COULD
JUST KIND OF FORGET
THAT I TOLD YOU THIS?
WELL, I KIND OF HAVE TO,
I MEAN, 'CAUSE THE THING IS...
WELL, THE THING IS...
THAT... YOU KNOW, THAT
YOU'RE MARRIED TO EMILY.
THAT IS WHAT THE THING IS.
OH, GOD.
THING... ROSS...
THINGS AREN'T GOING TO BE
WEIRD BETWEEN US, RIGHT?
I MEAN, WAS THAT JUST
THE STUPIDEST THING,
ME TELLING YOU THAT?
NO, NO, NO.
GOD, I MEAN, I'M GLAD YOU DID.
LOOK, IF-IF NOTHING ELSE,
IT'S-IT'S ALWAYS GREAT
WHEN SOMEONE TELLS YOU
THEY LOVE YOU.
R... THAT'S WHAT I SAID!
ROSS, THANK YOU
FOR BEING SO NICE.
NO, THANK YOU FOR...
THANK YOU.
( happy sigh )
OKAY, LET'S GO!
YEAH, ATLANTIC CITY!
Ross:
COME ON.
ATLANTIC CITY, BABY.
OOH, LET'S ROLL
SOME BONES.
HEY, JOEY
HIGH-FIVE FOR ROLLING BONES.
( howling )
OW!
OH!
UH, PHEEBS,
YOU'RE LEAKING.
OH, MY GOD,
YOUR WATER BROKE.
OH... OKAY.
OH...
ALL RIGHT,
WELL, DON'T WORRY.
I CALL SHOTGUN.
PHEEBS!
WE HAVE TO TAKE YOU
TO THE HOSPITAL NOW.
Ross:
PHEEBS
PHEEBS, THE BABIES
ARE COMING NOW.
HONEY, HIGH-FIVE,
THE BABIES ARE COMING.
( whooping )
HEY, WAIT...
REMEMBER WHEN MY WATER BROKE?
( whooping )
PHOEBE'S GOING TO
HAVE HER BABIES.
I KNOW, IT'S...
BEAUTIFUL AND AMAZING.
YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE
I CAN'T BELIEVE?
I HAD TO KISS PHOEBE AND RACHEL
EVERY TIME I LEFT THE ROOM.
I MEAN, IT'S TOO BAD
THEY DIDN'T SEE US HAVING SEX.
DO YOU KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT WOMEN?
NO.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
[Captioned by The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]